[{"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 3, "asentId": 4}, {"question": " how\u0092d it go with pete?!", "answer": " tell us!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " yeah, could you scooch?", "answer": " yeah, move over just a little bit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " why? why?! what\u0092s wrong with me?!", "answer": " what\u0092s the matter?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " how do you know?", "answer": " well y'know, he\u0092s got access.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " y'know it\u0092s that feeling you get, y'know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " like when you go bowling and you know you\u0092re in somebody else\u0092s shoes?", "answer": " that\u0092s the one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " all right, so, so you went to pete\u0092s...", "answer": " what happened?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " so it\u0092s-it\u0092s not heeled yet?", "answer": " no-no, it\u0092s ooozing, oozing.  could you pass me the cream? is there any--oh, there\u0092s the cream.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " thomas, this is gonna be hard, but i wanted it to come from me, and nobody else.", "answer": " what is it, tim?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " it\u0092s me, i\u0092ve been sleeping with your wife.", "answer": "  so you\u0092re the gynaecologist?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": "  hey, i\u0092m trying to have a private conversation! is that okay?!", "answer": "  ooh,  can i have a napkin, please? could you please hand me a napkin?  would you--give me this thing  all right!! enough!  and you are no longer my friend! we are finished!  nada!! no more! you are a bastard for doing this!!  get away from me!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " so monica, what were you gonna tell us?", "answer": "  i have no idea. opening credits", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " so, come on, what was the big news pete wanted to tell you mon?! or should i say mrs. monica becker?", "answer": " no-no-no oh, keep your name, don\u0092t take his name.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " he didn\u0092t ask me to marry him.", "answer": " ohh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " well then definately don\u0092t take his name.", "answer": " he wanted to tell me he\u0092s gonna compete is some ultimate fighting competition thingy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " pete?!", "answer": " why?! what is it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know exactly. it\u0092s-it\u0092s sorta like wrestling.", "answer": "  oh?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " yeah, but without the costumes.", "answer": "  oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " and it\u0092s not fake, it\u0092s totally brutal.", "answer": " yeah, it\u0092s two guys in a ring, and the rules are: \u0093they\u0092re are no rules.\u0094", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " so you can like, bite, and pull people\u0092s hair and stuff?", "answer": " yeah, anything goes, except ah, eye gouging and fish hooking.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " what\u0092s fish hooking?", "answer": " huh, what\u0092s fish hooking...   thanks man, that would have been really hard to describe. what is that taste?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " so thanks for the warm welcome. it\u0092s good to have you guys on my team, and i come to play. i hope you do too. now, let\u0092s go out there and get \u0091em! huh? and remember, there is no \u0091i\u0092 in team.", "answer": " yes, but there\u0092s two in martini, soo everybody back to my office.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": "  you! chuckles! what\u0092s your name?", "answer": " oh it\u0092s bing, sir. i\u0092m sorry , i was just ah...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": "  that\u0092s right, ryder. wynona ryder for six.  thank you.   yeah, we have the reservations.", "answer": " yes!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": "  dude, what are you doing?", "answer": " thank you! today, my boss keep slapping my butt and he was acting like it was no big deal.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " yeesh, what\u0092d you do about it?", "answer": " well, i didn\u0092t do anything. i didn\u0092t want to be the guy who has a problem with his boss slapping his bottom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " i gotta tell ya, i think it\u0092s okay to be that guy.", "answer": " yeah, maybe it\u0092s like y'know, that jock thing. y'know how football players pat each other after touchdowns.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " y'know i don\u0092t, i don\u0092t understand guys, i mean i-i would never congratulate monica on a great stew by y'know, grabbin\u0092 her boob.", "answer": " yeah, i know, for a really great stew you just y'know, stick your head in between \u0091em.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " okay, can we please go eat?", "answer": " yeah. what are we getting?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": "  anything but stew.", "answer": " all right so, chandler, from now on, don\u0092t give your boss a chance to get you. y'know just ah, don\u0092t turn your back to him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " yeah, or you can teach him a lesson. y'know? what you could do is you could rub something that really smells on your butt, all right? then, when he goes to smack ya, his hand will smell.  now what could you rub on your butt that would smell bad?", "answer": "  what if joey were president?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " umm, hey rach, can i ask you something?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " okay, you can totally say no, but umm, would it be okay with you if i set ross up on a date?", "answer": " oh, ah with who?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " umm, my friend, bonnie. she just always thought ross was really cute, and now that you two aren\u0092t together, she asked if i could set it up, but if you\u0092re not cool with it...", "answer": " oh-oh-oh, which one is bonnie again?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " you remember her from my birthday party two years ago. she\u0092s yeah, like, average height, medium build, bald...", "answer": " oh!  that\u0092s fine.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " you are iron. you are steel! let me ask you something, how come when i call your computer support line, i have to wait an hour and a half?", "answer": " i told you, we\u0092re adding new operators all the time. could we concentrate on my training?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " it\u0092s just hard when i know i have e-mail i can\u0092t get!", "answer": "  hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " monica!  hi honey.", "answer": " all right, on the table.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " hey, umm, so listen umm, my friends were telling me a little about this ah, ultimate fighting thing and it, well it sounds really dangerous. i-i don\u0092t want you to get hurt, \u0091cause i kinda like you.", "answer": " oh, believe me, i don\u0092t want to get hurt either. i\u0092m being smart about this. see these guys? they\u0092re the best trainers in the world, and hoshi here used to be a paid assassin.  a house painter! he used to be a house painter.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " promise me you\u0092ll be careful.", "answer": " i promise.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " hey, are we still on for tonight?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " okay, good, \u0091cause umm, well maybe we could have a little workout of our own...", "answer": " no! no boom-boom before big fight!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": "  well that was depressing, i think i just bought a soft pretzel from one of the kids from fame. ready to go to the movies?", "answer": " um-hmm. oh wait! this is bonnie.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " this is bonnie?  this is bonnie?  you\u0092re bonnie?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " i can show you an id if you want?", "answer": " oh no, i\u0092m sorry, you look a lot different from the last time i-i saw you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " oh yeah, well i just started wearing bras again.", "answer": " oh, that must be it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": "  well i hope you have fun tonight.", "answer": " thanks! you too.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": "  you said she was bald.", "answer": " yeah, she was bald, she\u0092s not now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " how could you not tell me that she has hair?", "answer": " i don\u0092t know, i hardly ever say that about people.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": "  ohh, well, this is just perfect!", "answer": " well i\u0092m sorry, i thought you said it was okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " yeah, i said what was okay when i thought she was some weird bald chick. i mean, y'know, that girl has hair got all over head!", "answer": " well, maybe it won\u0092t work out. maybe ross won\u0092t like her personality.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 133, "asentId": 134}, {"question": " why, does she have a bad personality?", "answer": " oh no, bonnie\u0092s the best!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": "  what is with him?", "answer": " with him? you\u0092re is favourite, you\u0092re his guy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " we never get smacked.", "answer": " well, that\u0092s not true, he-he smacked you once.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " not on purpose, he ricocheted of you and got me.", "answer": " i\u0092m telling you, i need some smacks. i got a kid starting dartmouth in the fall.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": "  dartmouth? who went to dartmouth? dartmouth sucks. did you go to dartmouth bing?", "answer": " no sir.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " god ross, what is that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " yeah, it\u0092s the ultimate fighting combo. yeah, i saved thirty cents, plus i get to keep the cup. yay!!", "answer": " from new york city, new york! appearing in his ultimate fighting championship debut! he\u0092s known for his confrontational business style. ladies and gentlemen, introducing pete beck-errrr!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " i love you, pete!!!", "answer": " and his opponent, from hunnington beach, california! he\u0092s a 300 pound street fighter, tank abbottttttt!!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": "  pete! pete!! that guy\u0092s pretty huge!", "answer": " don\u0092t worry, hoshi taught me how to use an opponent\u0092s strength and weight against him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " all right! you go get him! let\u0092s go!", "answer": " here we go gentlemen, here we go!  are you ready?   are you ready?  let\u0092s get it on!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " hey!  it\u0092s me. mon-i-ca! can i just tell you how proud i am of you.", "answer": " it would be nice after hearing 20,000 people chant \u0093you suck!\u0094", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " i mean i-i thought you were nuts at first, but you-you did it. and now you can just look back at this thing with no regrets.", "answer": " what, look back?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " well, you\u0092re not gonna get going are you?", "answer": " well let me ask you a question. am i the ultimate fighting champion?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " well, no. but...", "answer": " well i\u0092m not gonna stop until i\u0092m the ultimate fighting champion.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " that guy stood on your neck until you passed out!", "answer": " let me tell you a story. when i set out to create moss 865, do you think it just happened overnight? no. there was moss 1, that burnt down my dad\u0092s garage, there was moss 2 that would only schedule appointments in january, and 862 others that i learned from, just like i learned from this fight, never to let a guy stand on my neck.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " you didn\u0092t know that already?", "answer": " look, i\u0092m gonna get better. okay? i promise you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " okay, just get a lot better.  fast.", "answer": " oh, one other thing. hoshi thinks that you being ringside may have affected my concentration.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey! how long until pete\u0092s fight?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " oh, about five minutes. right now they\u0092re interviewing his opponent. apparently he trains by going to iran and pulling the arms off thieves.", "answer": " hot dog?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " so ross, how umm, how did it go with bonnie?", "answer": " what? oh! i gotta tell you, i-i wasn\u0092t expecting to like her at all, i mean i actually wasn\u0092t expecting to like anyone right now, but she\u0092s really terrific.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " ohh, that\u0092s too bad!", "answer": " no, i-i\u0092m saying i liked her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " yeah, y'know what, there are other fish in the sea.", "answer": " pheebs, i think she\u0092s great. okay? we\u0092re going out again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " okay, i hear you! are you capable of talking about any thing else?", "answer": "  hey! which one\u0092s my turkey burger?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " ahh, the one next to my foot. sorry.", "answer": "  hey, the fight\u0092s starting!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " okay, we\u0092ll be right in.  so ah, did your boss try to slap you again today?", "answer": " nine times! okay, i had to put on lotion! but, it\u0092s gonna be okay, because as of tomorrow i\u0092m conducting an experiment, and if all goes as planned, my butt will be smack free.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " excuse me, doug?  hey there sports fan!!", "answer": "  bing! you got those numbers for me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " no, i ah, i didn\u0092t do them.", "answer": " oh, you forgot?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " no, no i just ah, didn\u0092t do them. instead, i ah, hung out with a couple of friends and had a couple of beers so i certainly don\u0092t deserve any praise, verbal or otherwise.", "answer": " well, i got tanked myself last night. pretty dicey drive home, tapanzi bridge never looked smaller.  that\u0092s okay, you\u0092re still my number one guy!  bing!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 203, "asentId": 204}, {"question": " doug!!", "answer": " hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " i\u0092m a little bit uncomfortable with the that way you express yourself.", "answer": " oh, is it the swearing? i mean is it the constant swearing? because i gotta tell ya, if it is, you can just... kiss my ass!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " no, no. it-it\u0092s not about the swearing, it\u0092s more about ah, the way, that you ah, occasionally, concentrate, your enthusiasm on my buttock.", "answer": " oh?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " oh, and don\u0092t get me wrong, i appreciate the sentiment. it\u0092s just that i, i have a rather, sensitive posterior, and ah, besides, it\u0092s making all the other guys jealous.", "answer": " well, say no more. y'know it takes guts to bring this up. bing! you\u0092re okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " ha!  ahhhhhhh!", "answer": " ahhhhh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " okay. would you rather live in the shirt pocket of a sweaty giant, or inside his shower drain?", "answer": "  oh my god! phoebe look, it\u0092s ross and that girl.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " no! no! look at that!  it\u0092s a line of ants! they\u0092re working as a team!", "answer": " phoebe!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": "  right, oh yeah. wow, oh, it looks like ross is breaking up with her. uff, i hope he lets her down easy. let\u0092s go.", "answer": " come on phoebe, look at that! they are not breaking up, look at them. okay that\u0092s, you know what that is? that is a, that is a second date, that\u0092s what that is! look at that, she just put her hand on his thigh...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " oh no! that really is nothing, she is very sexually aggressive.", "answer": " ohh!  phoebe, this is all your fault! now he loves her, he\u0092s gonna marry her, and this is all your fault.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " you said it was okay!", "answer": " you said she was bald!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " what?! what-what-what-what-what?!!", "answer": " phoebe, we can\u0092t, we just can\u0092t just let it happen! okay, we have to do something! we have to break them up! okay? just go in there and like, shave her head! you owe me one bald girl!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " okay, first of all, breathe. second of all, i don\u0092t get it. aren\u0092t you the one that decided that you didn\u0092t want to be with ross?", "answer": "  yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " well isn\u0092t he your friend? don\u0092t you want him to be happy?", "answer": " yes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " so?", "answer": " i just y'know, i didn\u0092t expect him to be this happy so soon. ufff. ooo-ooh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": "  oh no.", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " oh, we killed them all.", "answer": " oh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " it\u0092s okay, it\u0092s not as bad as it looks, it\u0092s a precaution. ah, i\u0092m not supposed to move my spine.", "answer": " please tell me you\u0092re stopping now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " i\u0092m fine! i\u0092d fight tonight, if they\u0092d let me.  see this circle i\u0092m marking off here? this is my zone of terror.", "answer": " you are insane! you-you gotta give this up!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " i can\u0092t until i\u0092m the ultimate fighter. i will do it. i\u0092m telling you, the day will come when children will argue over who will win a fight, me or superman. now, i\u0092m not saying i could beat superman, but y'know, kids are stupid.", "answer": " sit down. all right? please, just listen to me. you are terrible at this! okay? you are the worst ultimate fighter ever! ever!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " y'know i have a torn rotator cuff, a hairline fracture in my right forearm, and a severely bruised adam\u0092s apple, but that really hurt.", "answer": " well then, y'know what? i care about you to much to watch you hurt yourself like this. so if you have to do this, then you\u0092re gonna have to do it without me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " well if you\u0092re asking me to quit, then you\u0092re asking me to be someone i\u0092m not. i\u0092ve got to do this.", "answer": " then i\u0092ve gotta go. bye.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " mon-monica?", "answer": " yes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " thank you, sir.", "answer": "  oh, excuse me. i forgot my briefcase y'know, by accident.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " of course, you did. forgot something else too ya bastard!   well, what about you? you\u0092re not feeling left out or anything are ya?", "answer": " no. no, not at all, that\u0092s-that\u0092s ridiculous.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " everybody else got one, and you want one too. don\u0092t you?", "answer": " ye-ye-yeah, yes i do!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " pete becker is circling the ring now. it looks like, he\u0092s just trying to feel him out. oh, bruiser is just...", "answer": " run! run you crazy, rich freak!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " check it out, he\u0092s winning!  pete\u0092s winning!", "answer": " really?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " no-o-o!!", "answer": " uh-oh, bruiser has becker on the canvas and is going for his favourite area.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " wait, if that\u0092s his favourite area, why is he being so mean to it?", "answer": " well, this is ironic. of your last two boyfriends, richard didn\u0092t want to have kids, and from the looks of it, now pete can\u0092t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s3/ep24.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}]